{
    "subject": "resource/Adam_Kotsko",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Flint,_Michigan",
    "human_readable": "Adam Kotsko was born in Flint, Michigan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8604256510734558,
            "question": "Where was Adam Kotsko born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7597630620002747,
            "question": "Is Flint a significant place in Adam Kotsko's story?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6797683835029602,
            "question": "What city is associated with Adam Kotsko's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5742800235748291,
            "question": "What state is Flint, Michigan in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49366509914398193,
            "question": "Does Adam Kotsko have any family ties to Flint?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4426513612270355,
            "question": "Where might Adam Kotsko have grown up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4419387876987457,
            "question": "What are some possible connections between Flint and Adam Kotsko?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4083224833011627,
            "question": "Are there any notable figures from Flint, Michigan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31398093700408936,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Adam Kotsko?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3092716932296753,
            "question": "Is there anything else known about Adam Kotsko's early life?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Adam Kotsko was born in Flint, Michigan.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3721_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Adam Kotsko?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3721_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable figures from Flint, Michigan?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3721_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some possible connections between Flint and Adam Kotsko?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3721_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3721_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3721_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3721_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3721_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3721_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3721_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3721_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3721_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3721_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3721_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3721/re-ranker-msmarco/57.txt explicitly states that \"Adam Kotsko was born in Flint, Michigan\", and another document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3721/re-ranker-msmarco/24.txt mentions Adam Kotsko's birth year as 1980."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information states that \"Adam Kotsko was born in Flint, Michigan,\" which matches the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}